Communications Workers of America (CWA), Local 1104, Education Division; Records apap132
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Financial Papers, 1982-2000; Undated; 4; 0.8 cubic ft.
  - State University of New York at Buffalo Academic Affairs Annual Report and Planning, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 17)
  - Steering Committee Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 18)
  - Taxes and Student Stipends, 1974-1975; 1982 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 19)
  - Tuition Waivers, 1976; 1981-1982; 1995 (Box 2 (4-Financial Papers), Folder 20)
- Publications, 1982-2000; Undated; 5; 0.6 cubic ft.
  These are a variety of newsletters published by the individual GSEU branches at each SUNY school as well as non-union publications that featured union news. There are also two folders of the GSEU Notes, which originated with the statewide executive committee and changed in appearance frequently over the years. Runs of any given publication are sporadic; there are none which have every issue. Of particular note for missing issues are: the Buffalo Times, the Graduate Quill, the GSEU Notes, the NYS Student Leader, and the Union Times.
  - Buffalo Americanist Digest, 1997 April; 1997 November; 1998 Spring (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Buffalo Times, 1994-1997; 1999 Spring; 1999 Fall (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Campus Voice, 1996 Summer (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 3)
  - The Current, 1983 November (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Gradline, 1995 February-1995 March; 1995 July; 1996 January (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 5)
  - The Graduate Post, 1983 February-1983 December; 1985 October-1987 March; 1990 December (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 6)
  - The Graduate Quill, 1991 October-1996 January (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 7)
  - The GSEU-Albany Newsletter, 1996 January (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 8)
  - The GSEU- Binghamton Newsletter, 1995 February (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 9)
  - GSEU Newsletter, 1974 November-1976 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 10)
  - GSEU Notes, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 11)
  - GSEU Notes, 1984; 1985 September; 1987 April; 1996 January; Undated (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 12)
  - GSO News and Blues, 1990 October; 1991 February (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Graduate Student News, 1992 September; 1993 March (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 14)
  - Labor Activist, 1994 February; 1995 November-1995 December (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 15)
  - The Opinion: SUNY Buffalo School of Law, 1992 September (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 16)
  - Stony Brooks State of the Union, 1992 April (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 17)
  - Student Leader, 1990 (Box 2 (5-Publications), Folder 1)
  - The Union Rag, 1993 May (Box 2 (5-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Union Times, 1991 October-1994 Fall (Box 2 (5-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Union Times, 1994 Spring-Fall; 1996 February-1996 December; 1998 February-2000 Spring (Box 2 (5-Publications), Folder 4)
- Subject Files, 1969-2001; Undated; 6; 5.0 cubic ft.
  Contains material from affiliated groups including the Graduate Student Organization (GSO), Student Association of the State University of New York (SASU), and Staff Association, all of which worked closely with the GSEU on matters of mutual interest. The success of the SUNY GSEU caused the local 1104 to become a model for organizers from schools in other states; the archivist retained any files from those schools that showed evidence of contact with the SUNY GSEU in this collection. Projects and causes that affected the group statewide can be found in this series, such as campaigning against sweatshop labor used for SUNY merchandise and the Citizens Mobilization efforts of the mid-1990s that protested the state budget situation. Many of the files related to healthcare and health insurance for student employees are in this series as well.
  - Agreement Between the State of New York and GSEU/CWA, Local 1188, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Albany County Federation of Labor Meeting Minutes, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - American Arbitration Association  SUNY Albany vs. GSEU Local 1188, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Anecdotal Survey Data, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - April Fools Day Press Release, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Answers to Common Questions Revisions, 1984 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Appeals to Chancellor D. Bruce Johnstone, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Association of Graduate Student Employees: Berkeley, CA, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - At the Eye of the Storm - Graduate Employees Organization Bargaining Handbook, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Bargaining Survey  Draft, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Bargaining Survey Information, 1992; 1994 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Bargaining Survey: Raw Numbers for Spring 1995 Negotiations (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Bargaining Training Plan, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Binghamton Council Resolution, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Booklet - Electing Union Officers, 1980 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Booklet - Election of Officers of Labor Organizations, 1978 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Buffalo Fact Finding Survey, 1982 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Buffalo Orientation Materials, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Buffalo - Safety Conditions: Radiation, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Buffalo State Advisory Panel, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Buffalo State and Fredonia: Information on Joining GSEU, 1992; 1994-1996; Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Casual Positions - Inclusion in Collective Bargaining, Albany, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Certification Election Materials, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Certification Task Force - Draft Prospectus: University Graduate Teaching Assistant Certificate Program at the University at Buffalo, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Chants/Songs, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Child Care, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Citizen Action Program, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Citizens Mobilization to Save New York, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Constitution of the United Graduate Student Organizations (UGSO) of SUNY, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Contract Mobilization and Overall Organizer/Staff Training, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Contract Negotiation Struggle: SUNY Buffalo News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - CWA New Members Kit, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - CWA Uniform Operating Practices Manual, Sections 1-10, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - CWA Uniform Operating Procedures Manual, Sections 11-14, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - CWA Uniform Operating Procedures Manual, Sections 15-24, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Demonstration Scenarios, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Democratic Socialists of America, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Fee Information, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Final Report and Analysis of Targeted Departments - Stony Brook, 1991 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Financial Aid and Tax Help - GSEU International Student Committee Buffalo, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Gottfried Bill, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Governor Cuomo Radio Conversation SUNY Buffalo, 1983 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Graduate Student Association: Testimony to Senate & Assembly Higher Education Committees, 1985 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Graduate Student Employee Health Plan - Member Handbook, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Graduate Student Organizing: Examining the Issues by J. Villa, 1991 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Graduate Student Organization - Grant Materials, Resolutions, etc., 1991-1992 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Grant Proposal Workshop, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Grant Writing Committee Info, 1990; 1992-1993 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Grievance Forms and Worksheets, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - GSA vs. Rossberg - Salary, 1981-1982 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - GSEU Answers to Common Questions, 1984 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - GSEU Fact Sheet - Draft, Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - GSEU Fact Sheets, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - GSEU Flyer/Handout Master Copies, 1992-1994; Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 5-6)
  - GSEU Flyers and Handouts - Early Organizing, ca. 1980-1985 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - GSEU Flyers/Handouts, 1982-1985; 1990-1996 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - GSEU Flyers/Handouts, 1997-2001 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - GSEU Flyers/Handouts, Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 10-11)
  - GSEU Newsletter Guidelines and Summer 1995 Copy of Talking Union (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - GSEU versus SUNY Buffalo - Improper Practice Charge, Elimination of SILS GA Positions, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - GSO Flyers and Brochures, 1998; Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Guidelines & Contracts for Other Schools, 1969; 1981-1982; Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Guidelines & Contracts for Other Schools, 1982; Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Guidelines & Contracts for Other Schools: Note cards, Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Handbook for Graduate & Teaching Assistants SUNY Buffalo, 1996 Fall (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Health Care Grievance Information, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Healthcare Information - Albany, 1996-1999 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Health Insurance - Act to Amend Health Fee Waiver, 1991 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Health Insurance Bid Request, 1994 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 22-23)
  - Health Insurance Fees and Plans, 1990-1995 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Health Insurance for Graduate Students - Faculty Letters of Support, 1991 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Health Insurance Issues - Buffalo, 1994-1996 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Health Insurance - Univera Plan, 1999-2000 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Health Plan Options, 1994 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - History of Negotiations Between GSEU and SUNY Albany Parking Issues, 1994 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Introduction to GSEU Overheads, Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Instructions for Filling Out Weekly Mobilization Reports, Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Issues and Demands of the GSEU, Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Issues: Health Care and Affirmative Actions, 1982; 1984-1985 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Ithaca - Union Conference, 1991 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Labor History and Organizing Materials, Chris Vestuto, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Labor - Religion Coalition and the GSEU, 2000; Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Lets Get Personnel Campaign, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Lobbying Tips and NYS Legislature and Fact Sheets, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Lorenzetti and Lawyers Rep Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Made in U.S.A. Labor Cartoons with Autographs & Messages from Artists, 1993 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Memorandum: Mandatory Student Activity Fees/External Non-Profits, 1980 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Michigan Organizing, 1981-1982 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Michigan Organizing - Ann Arbor, 1981/1987 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Middle States Evaluation - Final Report to Buffalo, 1982 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Mobilization Workshop - Tom Reifer, Local 1188, 1995 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - "Mobilizing for the 90s Handbook with Staff Training Notes, 1995 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Need for GA/TA Job Descriptions, 1983 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Negotiating Tips and Preliminary Analysis of Governors Executive Budget, 1995 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - New Paltz Budget Issues - Art Department, 1993 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Binghamton, 1983 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings - General, 1984 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings - General, 1982-2000 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Stony Brook, 1983 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - New York Giants - GSEU Protest of Negotiations, 1996 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - New York Public Employees Fair Employment Act - Taylor Law, Undated (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Notebooks, unidentified, Undated (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Notebooks, unidentified, ca. 1999 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - NYS Senate Democratic Task Force on Future of Affordable Higher Education in NYS - Public Hearing, 1996 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Organizing Materials, 1980-1984; Undated (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Organizing Materials: Other Schools, 1992; Undated (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 19-20)
  - Parking Agreements at Buffalo and Albany, 1996 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Parking Issues - Arbitration, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 22-24)
  - Parking Fee Negotiations - Buffalo, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Parking Fee Negotiations - Buffalo, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Parking Fee Proposals and Negotiations - Buffalo, 1996 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Parking Negotiations - Cost Models, 1994 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Parking Fee Resolution -- Stony Brook, 1989 (Box 3 (6-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Parking Fee Survey -- Buffalo, Undated (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Parliamentary Procedure/ How to Present a Motion/ Robert's Rules, 1996; Undated (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Payless Payday/ G.A.-T.A. Raises at Buffalo, 1982-1983 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Paxon Protest -- Arrests at Buffalo/ Amherst, 1996 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - PERB -- Cases on Behalf of Groups, 1984; 1991; 1995-1996 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - PERB - Correspondence, 1981-1984; 1994-1995; 2000 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - PERB History with Public Employees, 1991; 1993-1994 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - PERB Improper Practice Charge Material and Glossary, Undated (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - PERB - Miscellaneous Meeting Notes, 1982; 1985 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - PERB - Taylor Law Booklets, 1973; 1974; Undated (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Petition Circulators, Undated (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Phone Raps and Procedures, 1998; Undated (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Phone Script and Reference Q and A for Contract Vote, 1996-1999 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Political Action Committee of Graduate Student Association at Buffalo, 1990; 1994-1995 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Press Releases, 1992-1999 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Provosts Graduate Awards - Discrimination Issues, Binghamton, 1996 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Public Hearings - Frankie Condons Testimony, 1996 February (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Relatively Complete Guide to 1992-1993 GSEU Resolutions (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Rethinking SUNY Draft Proposals, 1995 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - "Rethinking SUNY" Campaign, 1996 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Right to Grievance Procedures, 1996 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - SASU Executive Impact Statement (1982) and Fact Sheet, Undated (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - SASU, GSEU, NYPIRG, CUNY Student Solidarity Conference, 1996 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - SASU Response to the Governors Budget, 1995 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Sexual Harassment Committee, Buffalo, 1998 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Sims, Kathleen - Project Renaissance, 1998-1999 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Solidarity Campaigns, 1995-1996 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Staff Association Agreements with GSEU, 1995-1997 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Staff Association Agreements with GSEU, 1997-1999 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Staff Association Contract Proposal (1993) and Amendments, 1996 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Staff Association of GSEU Charter, 1992 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Staff/ GSEU Bargaining - Officers and Counter Offers, 1994 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - State Budget Battles, 1996 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - State Budget: GSEU and Citizens Mobilization Save New York Day, 1996 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 34-35)
  - State Budget - SUNY Cuts, 1996 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 36-37)
  - State Budget: SUNY Cuts/ United University Professions Documents, 1996-1997 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - State Proposals for Negotiations with the GSEU - NYS GOER, 1995 May (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - State University of New York Graduate & Teaching Assistants  Albany Area, 1999 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Stony Brooks Future: A Draft Plan, 1996 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Student Association Files - Chris Vestuto, 1990 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Student Employee Health Plan Labor/ Management Meeting, 1996 July (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Student Solidarity Conference: Advocating & Organizing for Higher Education, 1996 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Student Employee Health Plan Labor/ Management Meeting, 1996 (Box 4 (6-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - SUNY Degree Program Reduction, 1996 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - SUNY Policy on Student Activity Fees, 1976 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Tabling Materials, 1990; Undated (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Teaching Assistant Responsibilities - Psychology, Buffalo, 1996 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Teaching Assistants Association of Wisconsin and the SUNY GSEU, 1983-1986; Undated (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Teaching Assistants Association: University of Wisconsin  Madison, Agreement and Membership Handbook, 1997-1999 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Technology Fee, Buffalo  Negotiating Notes and Ground Rules, 1996 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Technology Fee Negotiations, Albany and Buffalo, 1997 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Things We Do Memo Outlining Officer Responsibilities, Undated (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Thoughts on the Founding of the Labor Party by L. Rockenbach, 1996 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Toronto Organizing - Canadian Union of Educational Workers, 1981-985; Undated (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - UAlbany Dirty Laundry Campaign, 1999 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - UAlbany Early Organizing Materials, 1984 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - UAlbany Sweatfree/Sodhexo Protests, 1999-2000 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - UGSO Constitution and Revisions, 1991; Undated (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - UGSO Contract and Personnel Policy, 1991 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - UGSO Correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - UGSO  General Material, 1990-1992 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - UGSO: Minutes & By-Laws of the United Graduate Student Organizations of SUNY, 1991 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - UGSO Meeting Minutes, Undated (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - UGSO Official Statement of Purpose and Strategy Chart, Undated (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - UGSO Projects Director Contract & Personnel Policy, 1993 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - UGSO Resolutions, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - UGSO/GSEU Response to SUNY Office of Student Affairs Report on Student Health Servies, 1990 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - UGSO Summit Meetings I-V, 1989-1990 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - UGSO Summit Meetings VI, VII, IX, X, 1990-1991 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Union Privelege Benefits, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - University of Florida: Graduate Assistants United, 1982-1985 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - University of Iowa and GSEU: Tax-Exempt Issue, 1985 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Western New York Council, 1994 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Western New York Council on Occupational Safety and Health, 1995-1997 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Womens Issues at Buffalo, 1982; Undated (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Work Stoppage at Buffalo, 1991 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Working Conditions Survey, 1995 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Yale Memorial Day Rally, 1996 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Yale Strike - Background Info. And Organizing Materials, 1996 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Yale University T.A. Strike and Buffalo Support, 1996 (Box 5 (6-Subject Files), Folder 37)
- Photos and Memorabilia, 2000; Undated; 7; 0.6 cubic ft.
  Arranged by format.
  Series 7 contains an assortment of artifacts accumulated or created by the GSEU. Most are undated, such as the t-shirts and buttons, but are still a good representation of the opinions and actions of the group as a whole. Box one has most of the three-dimensional items while box two houses all of the photos. Only one package of pictures was labeled specifically by GSEU members with the event and date. Finally, there are two oversized folders with GSEU posters, some professionally printed while others are handmade.
  - Bumper Stickers, Undated (Box 1 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Item 1)
  - Buttons, Undated (Box 1 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Item 2)
  - Convention Nametags, Undated (Box 1 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Item 3)
  - Mug, Undated (Box 1 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Item 4)
  - Ribbons, Undated (Box 1 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Item 5)
  - Shirts, Undated (Box 1 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Item 6)
  - Stamp, Undated (Box 1 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Item 7)
  - Stickers, Undated (Box 1 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Item 8)
  - Citizen's Mobilization Photo, Undated (Box 2 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Folder 1)
  - Convention Photos, Undated (Box 2 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Folder 2)
  - State University--Buffalo GSEU Event Photos, Undated (Box 2 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Folder 3)
  - University at Albany Multi-Union Event Photos, Undated (Box 2 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Folder 4)
  - University at Albany GSEU Event Photos, Undated (Box 2 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Folder 5)
  - University at Albany Sodexho-Marriott Protest Photos, Undated (Box 2 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Folder 6)
  - University at Albany Sweatshop Protest Photos, Undated (Box 2 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Folder 7)
  - University at Albany Takeover of President's Office Photos, 2000 April 04 (Box 2 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Photos, Undated (Box 2 (7-Photos and Memorabilia), Folder 9)